&Manager Hanwen.
Okay, I know.
I've contacted the creditors in the group.
Someone should go to the school to corner him soon.
Spread the news about him
giving out loans on campus too.
Spread the news about the loans?
Is it necessary?
Mr. Wang is already investigating us in the student council.
These student loans will be discovered sooner or later.
Now is the best chance to clear our names.
I understand.
My dad is in the hospital because of the debt from this project!
And he has the nerve to go back to school like nothing happened!
Excuse me.
Do you know this person?
No, I don't.
The damage is quite serious.
I don't know to what extent it can be fixed.
Tell you what, I'll have someone take it apart and try.
Then when can I get it?
This afternoon.
This afternoon?
Should we go see a movie first?
Don't you have classes this afternoon?
I can ask for leave.
Plus, don't we have to wait for the phone to be fixed?
It's too much trouble to go back.
No.
I'll pick up the phone.
You go back to class first.
This is my number.
Call me when it's fixed.
I'll pick it up for her.
Okay.
Let's go.
It's rare that I've arranged the itinerary.
Zixi.
It's your birthday today.
Do you have any plans?
No.
Then.
Wait for me downstairs at the dorm tonight.
I have some gifts for you.
Oh.
What are you guys yelling about?
An Yufan.
Fine if we don't watch a movie,
but you should at least bring my phone back.
Seriously.
You told me to wait for you in the dorm.
I mean,
I've been waiting for you all day.
Now look.
I can't leave,
and I can't stay.
The cake and gifts are ready.
What else is missing?
I close my eyes and listen to your heartbeat and breathing.
And right now, it's just us on Earth.
The shape of your smiling lips always captivates my heart.
What does this mean?
Wow, what is going on?
Uncle He, aren't you in the hospital?
I came specifically to pick you up.
Someone is spreading rumors about you
and organizing creditors to block you at the school gate.
Block me at the school gate?
Why?
Someone wants to stir up news about you
to use you against your father.
I guess you won't be able to return to school for a while.
Pack your luggage and come back with me first.
Boss.
You usually practice with drafts.
Why not this time?
I had guidance from an expert.
Someone actually guided you?
I wasn't bold enough before,
so I had to keep practicing the draft.
Now,
I am ready.
You're not bold enough?
I mean, is this person reliable?
To chase girls.
You just need to be bold, attentive, and thick-skinned.
I'm just not bold enough.
Besides being bold,
you also need to be generous.
Especially when giving gifts, you must cater to their preferences.
That's what I thought too.
Simply put, things like jewelry
and bags.
But apart from gifts,
a sense of ceremony is also important.
Especially for occasions like birthdays,
there must be a romantic atmosphere.
I've taught you all my tricks.
You have to comprehend it well.
An Yufan.
Don't blame me for not waiting for you.
It's really too dangerous here.
I can't stay here for long.
Yin Zixi,
what are you doing here?
Here she comes.
Boss, Yin Zixi is out.
Oh no, I can't control myself again.
Oh no.
Zixi.
I like you.
Be my girlfriend.
Together! Together!
Yin Zixi.
I won't give her to you.
She is my girlfriend.
Are you okay?
What you just said,
is it true?
Yin Zixi.
I like you.
Assistant Casting Director Xi Chongjing
Props Assistant Li Kunxiao
Production Vehicle Yi Mingle
Yitong